actualized.org 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Actualized.org

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Any information we collect will be kept under technological lock and key, and used only to help you find the right insurance. Below you'll find our official privacy policy.

## Web Site Privacy Policy

This is the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") for the Actualized.org site (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy sets forth our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of certain information relating to your use of the Site. Your use of this Site signifies your understanding and acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Terms and Conditions, which govern your use of the Site in general.  

### Age Requirement for Use of Site

This Site is not intended for use by persons under the age of 16 years old. You must be 16 years old or older to provide any personal information to the Site, or to us through the Site.

### Domicile Requirement for Use of the Site

You represent and warrant that you are domiciled in the United States.  

## 1.  Collecting Information

### Personally Identifiable Information

The Site may request and collect certain personally identifiable information including, but not limited to, Application Data and other personal information contained in User Submissions, through various means such as online forms, online applications, e-mail and comments submitted to the Site. Such information collected through the Site may include financial information, health-related information, and other sensitive information. 

_Other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, and unless given permission by you to do so, we will not sell or disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties._

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information 

We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information via the Site, such as Site usage activity and preferences, also known as demographic or profile data.

### Why must you give so much personal information? 

Insurance companies establish their rates using a variety of criteria. Since we deal with hundreds of companies, we must ask you questions required by all of them to determine the most competitive match for you.   

### Notice of Consumer Report Practices

In some cases, insurance companies may need to obtain additional background information about you. As an example Consumer reports may be ordered in connection with your insurance application. These reports provide information that may assist in determining your eligibility for insurance and the price you may be charged. Consumer reports may also be used for updates, renewals or extensions of this insurance. The insurance company may also obtain and use a credit-based insurance score based on information contained in your credit report. The insurance company may use a third party in connection with the development of the insurance score.

### Site Technology

As with many Web sites, we may use "cookies" and/or other technology (e.g., web bugs, e-mail bugs, clear GIFs, web beacons and tracker GIFs) in the Site or in our communications with you to enhance the functionality of the Site and to make your transactions and other activities more convenient and efficient (collectively, "Tracking Technologies"). These technologies may vary, but in some cases may involve a small file stored locally on the computer used to access the Site, and may be used by us to store and collect information relating to your viewing and use of the Site and our correspondences with you. You may set your web browser software not to accept cookies, but, if so, certain functionality of the Site may be affected. We may collect your IP (Internet Protocol) address to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Site and identify our users. We may also use such technologies to remember user preferences or minimize the need for you to re-enter information.

Third parties (including, but not limited to, software vendors, advertisers and fulfillment companies) may also use Tracking Technologies by or through the Site. We have no control over what information such third parties track or collect, and we have no responsibility or liability for any tracking, data collection or other activities of such third parties.

## 2\. Usage and Sharing

We use information collected on and through this Site for a variety of purposes in the course of business and as otherwise set forth herein. For example, such information may be used to process your applications to receive quotations or to send you information about our and our affiliates' products and services and other information and materials that may be of interest to you. This information may also be used to evaluate what portions of the Site are more popular than others, determine where visitors came from, where they go, and how long they stay on a particular page, or the Site in general. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties.

Application Data may be forwarded to insurance agents, discount program representatives, brokers and/or companies who may contact you with a quote by email, telephone, postal mail or other forms of communication. We are not responsible, and shall not be liable, if an agent, broker, discount program representative or company to whom we forward your Application Data violates our Privacy Policy or their own privacy policy, if any.

We may disclose your personal information to companies that perform technology or marketing services for us for their use in performing such services. We may transfer, sell or assign aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about Site usage to third parties. We may transfer, sell or assign personal information to third parties as a result of a sale of all or substantially all of our assets relating to this portion of our business or in connection with a merger, consolidation, change in control, reorganization or liquidation. We also reserve the right to disclose any information concerning you if required by law or to protect or defend our rights or the rights or well-being of our users or if you are involved (or are reasonably suspected to be involved) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order.

## 3\. Security

The application form on the Site supports encryption to help protect the security of your transfer of data to the Site. Although we will take all reasonable security precautions regarding information stored on the Site, due to the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any information stored on our servers, or transmitted to or from a user, will be free from unauthorized access, and we disclaim any liability for any theft or loss of, unauthorized access or damage to, or interception of any data or communications. By using the Site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.

## 4\. Consent to Processing

By providing any personal information to this Site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the transfer of such personal information to, and the collection and processing of such personal information in, the United States and other countries or territories.

By submitting this information you are authorizing Brokers, Agents, discount program representatives and/or Insurance Professionals in the Actualized.org network to contact you directly with quotes via telephone, fax, and email, regardless of the presence of your phone number(s) on any local or national no-call list.

## 5\. Links

This Site may contain links or references to other Web sites outside of our control. Please be aware that we have no control over these sites and our privacy policy does not apply to these sites.

## 6\. Your Acceptance of this Policy

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time so visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.
